American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
- Series V. Affiliated Organizations, 1933-2002; bulk 1946-1991; 14 boxes (19.65 linear feet)
  - Subseries V.D. Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology (FASEB), 1933-1990, 2001; 201 folders
    - FASEB Public Information Committee 1971 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1971 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - FASEB Ad Hoc Committee for 2nd FASEB Conference Minutes 1972 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee and Executive Committee 1972 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1972 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - FASEB Meetings Committee 1972 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1972 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1972 (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee and Public Information Committee 1972 (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - FASEB Biology Data Book Editorial Board 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - FASEB Life Sciences Research Office (LSRO) Advisory Committee 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - FASEB/ASBC "Withdrawal General" from association with D.O.D. 1968 (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - FASEB Federation Board Minutes 1972-1973 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - FASEB Editorial Board 1973 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee and Executive Committee 1973 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - FASEB Meetings Committee 1973 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1973 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1973 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1973-1975 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee and Executive Committee 1974 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - FASEB Correspondence, Eugene Hess 1974 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee and Public Information Committee 1974 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1974 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - FASEB Select Committee on Priorities and Planning 1974-1975E (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - FASEB Cosmo Club Correspondence 1969-1977 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - FASEB LSRO Advisory Committee 1974 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - FASEB Long Range Planning Committee 1969 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - FASEB Executive Committee Meeting/Minutes 1969 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1969 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1970 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - FASEB William D. Garvey Grant Proposal Review 1970 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - FASEB House Committee 1970 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - FASEB Meetings Committee 1970 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1970 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - FASEB Programs Committee 1970, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 26)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1970-1972 (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - FASEB Editorial Board 1971, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1971 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1971 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee and Public Information Committee 1977 (Box 102, Folder 31)
    - FASEB Programs Committee 1977 (Box 102, Folder 32)
    - FASEB LSRO Advisory Committee 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - FASEB Constitution and Bylaws Revision 1978-1980 (Box 102, Folder 34)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee 1978 (Box 102, Folder 35)
    - FASEB Federation Board Meeting 1978 (Box 102, Folder 36)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1978 (Box 102, Folder 37)
    - FASEB New Building Correspondence and Questionnaire 1978 (Box 102, Folder 38)
    - FASEB New Building Project Materials 1978 (Box 102, Folder 39)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1978 (Box 102, Folder 40)
    - FASEB Correspondence, Robert W. Krauss 1979 (Box 102, Folder 41)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1979, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 42)
    - FASEB Editorial Board 1979-1980 (Box 102, Folder 43)
    - FASEB Annual Meeting Program 1980 (Box 102, Folder 44)
    - FASEB Constitution and Bylaws Revision 1980 (Box 102, Folder 45)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Board 1980 (Box 102, Folder 46)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1980 (Box 102, Folder 47)
    - FASEB LSRO Advisory Committee 1980 (Box 102, Folder 48)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1980 (Box 102, Folder 49)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1980 (Box 102, Folder 50)
    - FASEB Public Affairs 1980 (Box 102, Folder 51)
    - FASEB Williamsburg Retreat 1980 (Box 102, Folder 52)
    - FASEB Annual Report 1981 (Box 102, Folder 53)
    - FASEB Correspondence, M.J. Osborne, 1981 ("Missing Scientists Abroad" 1977- Argentina and USSR) (Box 102, Folder 54)
    - FASEB Creationism/Evolution Ballot 1981 (Box 102, Folder 55)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1981 (Box 102, Folder 56)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee and Executive Committee 1981 (Box 102, Folder 57)
    - FASEB Joint Meeting of Executive Committee and Federation Board 1981 (Box 102, Folder 58)
    - FASEB Meetings Committee 1981-1982 (Box 102, Folder 59)
    - FASEB Programs Committee 1981 (Box 102, Folder 60)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1981 (Box 102, Folder 61)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee and Public Information Committee 1981 (Box 102, Folder 62)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1982 (Box 102, Folder 63)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee and Executive Committee 1982 (Box 102, Folder 64)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1982 (Box 102, Folder 65)
    - FASEB Joint Meeting of Executive Committee and Federation Board 1982 (Box 102, Folder 66)
    - FASEB Program 1982 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1982 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee and Public Information Committee 1982 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - FASEB Annual Report 1983 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1983 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - FASEB Annual Report 1984 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - FASEB Education Committee 1984 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1984 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - FASEB Exhibits Advisory Committee 1984 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1984 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1984 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1984 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1984 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - FASEB Summer Research Conference 1984 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - FASEB Summary of Legislation 1985 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - FASEB Annual Report 1987 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - FASEB Joint Meeting, Federation Board and Executive Committee 1987 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1987 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - FASEB Annual Report 1988 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - FASEB Education Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1988 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - FASEB Joint Meeting, Federation Board and Executive Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - FASEB LSRO Advisory Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - FASEB Program Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - FASEB Summer Research Conference Advisory Committee 1988 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - FASEB Annual Report 1989 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - FASEB Executive Committee 1989 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1989 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1989 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - FASEB Joint Meeting, Program Committee and Meetings Committee 1989 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - FASEB LSRO Advisory Committee 1989 (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee Correspondence 1989 (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee Correspondence 1989 (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - FASEB Summer Research Conference Advisory Committee 1989 (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - FASEB Williamsburg Retreat Correspondence 1989 (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - FASEB Exhibit Booth 1990 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1990 (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - FASEB Health Insurance Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - FASEB Joint Meeting, Program Committee and Meetings Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - FASEB LSRO Advisory Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 46)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Correspondence 1990 (Box 103, Folder 47)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Correspondence 1990 (Box 103, Folder 48)
    - FASEB Transition Committee 1990 (Box 103, Folder 49)
    - FASEB Ad Hoc Group for Medical Research Funding 1991 (Box 103, Folder 50)
    - FASEB Affirmative Action Program 1991 (Box 103, Folder 51)
    - FASEB Conference on Biomedical Research Funding 1991 (Box 103, Folder 52)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee 1991 (Box 103, Folder 53)
    - FASEB Federation Board 1991 (Box 103, Folder 54)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1991 (Box 103, Folder 55)
    - FASEB/ASBMB Joint Annual Meeting 1991 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - FASEB Management Agreement 1991 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - FASEB Publications Committee 1991 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - FASEB Public Affairs Committee 1991 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - FASEB Executive Officer's Advisory Committee 1992 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - FASEB Finance Committee 1992 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - FASEB Newsletters 1990, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Subseries V.E. International Union of Biochemists (IUB), 1953-1990; 46 folders
    - IUB US National Committee 1953-1959 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1957 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - IUB Correspondence, Meetings & Agendas, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1963 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - IUB Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1964-1965 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - IUB Symposium 1962-1965 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - IUB-ASBC Atomic Models: Correspondence and Disbursements 1962-1967 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - IUB Programs Information 1962-1965 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - IUB US National Committee 1964-1965 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - IUB AD Hoc Committee for the Study of Future Biochemical Meetings 1964-1966 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - IUB "Conference on Spin Resonance in Biological Systems" 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - IUB US National Committee, 10th Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - IUB Council of Editors of Biology Journals 1966 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - IUB Affiliated Miscellaneous International Meetings 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - IUB 1967 Meeting, Tokyo, Japan: Correspondence and Minutes (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - IUB US National Committee 1969 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - IUB "Essays in Biochemistry" 1969-1976 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - IUB Correspondence 1970 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - IUB 1970 Meeting Minutes, Interlaken, Switzerland (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - IUB US National Committee 1970 (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - IUB Correspondence 1971 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - IUB Correspondence 1971, "The International Structure of Science" (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - IUB US National Committee 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - IUB US National Committee 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - IUB Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - IUB US National Committee 1975 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - IUB US National Committee 1976 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - IUB US National Committee Meeting Minutes and Correspondence 1983-1987 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - IUB Correspondence 1985-1988 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - IUB Interest Group Conference 1986 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - IUB US National Committee Meetings 1987, 19 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - IUB Correspondence 1988-1991 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - IUB Interest Groups 1989-1990 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - IUB US National Committee Meeting 1990 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry (IUPAC) Conferences 1960-1963 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - IUPAC/IUB Correspondence 1970 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - IUPAC/IUB CBN Publications 1972 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - IUPAC/IUB "Tentative Rules and Regulations of the Commission on Biochemical Nomenclature" 1973 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - IUPAC/IUB "Tentative Rules and Regulations of the Commission on Biochemical Nomenclature" 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - IUPAC/IUB "Tentative Rules and Regulations of the Commission on Biochemical Nomenclature and Related Documents" 1975 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Subseries V.F. Affiliated Organizations I- K, 1960-1988; 11 folders
    - ICSU Committee on Data for Sciences and Technology 1968 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - ICSU General Assembly 1976 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - International Scientific Organizations 1964 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - IEEE Conference on Scientific Journals 1975 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Keilin Memorial Fund and Lecture 1964 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Keystone Center, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Keystone Center, Plenary Sessions, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Keystone Center, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Keystone Center, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Keystone Center Forums, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Keystone Center, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Subseries V.G. Government Science Organizations: NAS, NRC, NIH, NLM, NSF, 1946-1991; 88 folders
    - NAS/NRC Committee for American Institutes of Biological Sciences 1947-1951 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Biology and Agriculture 1951-1959 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology 1952-1957 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology 1958-1959 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Biological Chemistry 1953-1954 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Biological Chemistry 1955 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Biological Chemistry 1957-1959 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - NAS/NRC Loyalty and Freedom of Science, Affiliated Organizations, 1954-1956 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - NAS/NRC IUB 1954-9156 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - NAS/NRC Report of the "Committee on Loyalty in Relation to Government Support of Unclassified Research" 1956 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Medical Sciences, Annual Reports, 1956-61 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology, Annual Reports, 1957-60 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - NAS/NRC Annual Reports 1957-58, 1963-64 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - NAS/NRC Office of Critical Tables 1958-1967 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Methods of Handling Chemical Information 1959-1962 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Biological Chemistry 1960-1967 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Biology and Agriculture 1960-1967 /td (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - NAS/NRC Advisory Committee on Chemical Notations Systems Project 1961 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - NAS/NRC Chemical Notations Systems Project 1961-1964 /td (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - NAS/NRC Participating Societies Correspondence 1962-1963 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - NAS/NRC Office of Biochemical Nomenclature 1962-1964 /td (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Modern Methods of Handling Chemical Information 1963-1967 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology, Annual Reports, 1963-64, 1967-69, 1973-74 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Medical Sciences, Annual Reports, 1962-64 /td (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Medical Sciences 1964 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology 1964 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - NAS/NRC Office of Biochemical Nomenclature 1965 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - NAS/NRC Advisory Committee on International Organizations 1965-1967 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on International Organizations 1965-1967 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology 1965-1966 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Medical Science (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - NAS/NRC Dates/Places of International Meetings 1966-1967 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - NAS/NRC Office of Biochemical Nomenclature 1966-1967 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Scientific and Technical Communication 1967 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - NAS/NRC Committee on Data and Science and Technology 1967 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - NAS/NRC Correspondence, Judith Werdel 1968 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - NAS/NRC Correspondence, Harte-Suridov, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - NAS/NRC Correspondence, Dr. Philip Handler 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - NAS/NAE Joint Commission 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - NAS/NRC Annual Meeting 1970 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - NAS/NRC General Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - NAS/NRC Division of Chemistry and Chemical Technology 1971-1973 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - NAS/NRC Pacific Science Association 1972 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - NAS/NRC General Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - NAS/NRC International Council of Scientific Unions, Commission on International Relations 1974 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - NAS/NRC General Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - NAS/NRC International Council of Scientific Unions, Commission on International Relations 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - NAS/NRC Executive Committee of the Office of Biochemical Nomenclature 1976-1977 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - NAS/NRC Draft Report 1980 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - NAS/NRC Assembly of Life Sciences 1983-84 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - National Foundation for the History of Chemistry 1990-1991 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - National Institute of Health (NIH) Proposal to the NIH for a Center on Medical Documentation and Communication Research 1963 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - NIH General Correspondence 1965-1970 (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - NIH Correspondence/Federal Support 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - NIH Copyright Policy 1971 (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - NIH Support Funds 1971 (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - NIH General Correspondence 1971-1976 (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - NIH Grant for ASBC Lecturer Recruiter Program 1977 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - National Conference on Health Research Principles 1978 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - National Library of Medicine (NLM) General 1962-1963 (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - NLM "Outline for a Study of American Biomedical Journal Financing" by Robert Harte, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - NLM Grant Application, William Stephenson 1963-1964 (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - NLM/NIH Grant Proposal Correspondence 1964 (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - NLM Legislation 1965 (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - National Institute of Nutrition, Annual Report, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - National Registry in Clinical Chemistry, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), Correspondence concerning Senate Bill 1850, Creation of NSF, 1946 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - NSF, Contract with FASEB, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Subseries V.H. Affiliated Organizations M-Z, 1943-1994; 24 folders
    - National Life Sciences Education Summit 1991 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - National Science Teachers and High School Science Programs 1991-1993 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Pan-American Association of Biochemical Societies (PAABS) General Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1971 (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1972 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1973 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1974 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1977-1980 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - PAABS Second General Congress 1978 (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - PAABS Fourth Congress 1984 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - PAABS General Correspondence 1985-1992 (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - The Pharmacologist 1994 (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - Photographs, Miscellaneous Portraits of Past Presidents (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Protein Society, "Protein Science" Agreement 1991 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Office of Biochemical Nomenclature Correspondence 1964-1966 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Office of Biochemical Nomenclature Correspondence 1967-1972 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Science Education 1991 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Terminal Systems Corporation 1984 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Triangle Coalition for Science and Technology, Newsletters 1989-1991, Incomplete (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - US Treasury Department 1986-1988 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Union of American Biological Societies 1943-1945 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Robert Welch Foundation, Annual Report 1966-1967 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - World Meetings Publications 1987 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - NSF General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - NSF Fellowships and Grants, 1961-1967 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - NSF General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - NSF "Space Filling Atomic Models" Project Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - NSF "Space Filling Atomic Models" Project Correspondence, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - NSF Grants and Contract Manuals, 1965-1966 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - NSF "Clarke Proposal" 1965 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - NSF Annual Report 1966 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - NSF Grants, 1968-1973 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - NSF General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - NSF Evaluative Report for NSF, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - NSF Conference Proposal 1973 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - NSF General Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - NSF General Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - NSF Grant Fund Project Reports 1976 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - NSF Science Information Activities Task Force 1977 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - NSF "Responses to 1986 Memo on Funding for 1987" (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - National Society for Medical Research 1963-1966 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - US Public Health Service, "Report of Delegation of American Biochemists to Russia" 1959 (Box 108, Folder 23)